well it finally happened we took the
tiny sentient human brains we grew in
jars and integrated them to
supercomputers and AI we already knew
that we could attach them to a computer
and we knew that they learned faster
than AI after all they beat our best
artificial intelligence at learning and
playing pong once scientists attached
the brain organoid to a computer chip
they allowed it to work unsupervised
with an AI program to learn it actually
worked they're able to take the neural
activity in the brain
and measure those electrical outputs and
code it into literal computer code but
as we've learned these are real life
forms they have similar brain activity
to a premature baby and we really don't
know much about their ability to make
decisions we do know that they have the
capacity to learn and if you watched my
little interview with cortical ABS they
believe they're sentient but not
conscious conscious as the ability to
perceive oneself I for one am not
looking forward to my computer having
matching depression with me or refusing
to let me pilot the discovery one
spacecraft I can't do that Dave